A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. (RBI) (and successors) records FA480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 3, 1948-1979; 3; 22.1 Cubic Feet 52 letter document boxes and 5 legal document boxes.; Standard storage boxes, Boxes 142-164.
  - Ventron Corp. - Financing - Exchange of Manion Stock for Ventron, 1966 (Box 384, Folder 2)
  - Ventron Corp. - Mergers, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - Ventron Corp. - Stock Option, 1971-1973 (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - Zapata - Annual Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 384, Folder 3)
  - Zapata - Board of Directors Meetings, 1961-1970 (Box 384, Folder 4)
  - Zapata - Rudy Ludt - Options, 1963-1970 (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - Zapata - Prospectus, 1969 (Box 384, Folder 6)
  - Zapata - Stockholder Meetings and Proxy, 1959-1970 (Box 385, Folder 1)
  - Zapata - General Correspondence, 1958-1964 (Box 385, Folder 2-4)
  - Zapata - General Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 387, Folder 1-5)
  - Zapata - Agreements, 1959 (Box 386, Folder 2)
  - Zapata - Renunciation of Loan Stock, 1964 (Box 386, Folder 3)
  - Zapata - Financial, 1959-1974 (Box 386, Folder 4)
  - Zapata - Seafarer Shipping Co. Financial, 1964-1970 (Box 386, Folder 5)
  - Zapata - Scandinavian Shipping Co. Financial, 1960-1970 (Box 386, Folder 6)
  - Zapata - Seafarer Tankers, 1965-1968 (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Zapata - Scandinavian American Shipping - Brostrom File, 1964-1969 (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - Zapata - Scandinavian American Shipping - Nova File, 1967-1968 (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - Zapata - Scandinavian American Shipping - Maersk File, 1963-1967 (Box 388, Folder 4)
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 4, 1941-1980; 4; 22.57 Cubic Feet 52 letter document boxes and 6 legal document boxes.
  - Archon Pure Products - Agreements, Annual Reports, Shareholders, 1971-1976 (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Archon Pure Products - Stock Purchase Agreement, 1971 (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Archon Pure Products - Financing Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 388, Folder 7)
  - Archon Pure Products - General, 1972-1975 (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Archon Pure Products - Lehman Brothers Investment Proposal, 1971 (Box 388, Folder 8)
  - Benmarl Vineyards - Mark Hiller, 1973-1977 (Box 388, Folder 9)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Investment Agreements, 1969 (Box 389, Folder 1)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Security Transactions, 1973 (Box 389, Folder 2)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Agreement, 1969 (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1972-1977 (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Handwritten Notes, 1974-1977 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    H.S. Smith.
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Financial - Audit, 1970-1972 (Box 389, Folder 6)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Financial Correspondence, 1969-1975 (Box 389, Folder 7)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Financial - Statements, 1975-1978 (Box 389, Folder 8)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Financing - Conference Memo, 1970 (Box 389, Folder 9)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Prospectus, 1969-1974 (Box 389, Folder 10)
  - Cambridge Memories, Inc. - Stockholders, 1977 (Box 389, Folder 11)
  - Central Trust Company, 1964 (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Cerro Corp. - Note Agreement, 1967-1972; 1972 (Box 390, Folder 3-4)
  - Cerro Corp. - Mergers, 1968-1976 (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Cerro Corp. - By-laws - Shareholders, Stockholders, 1966-1976 (Box 390, Folder 6)
  - Cerro Corp. - Closing, 1961 (Box 391, Folder 1)
  - Combustion Power Company, 1971-1974 (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Computone Systems, Inc. - Summary, 1967 (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Computone Systems, Inc. - Bankruptcy and Sale of LSR Stock, 1975-1976 (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Computone Systems, Inc. - Financial, 1966-1974 (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Computone Systems, Inc. - Financing, 1962-1968 (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Computone Systems, Inc. - Merger Proposals, 1963-1968 (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Computone Systems, Inc. - Shareholders, 1963-1965 (Box 392, Folder 4)
  - Continental Mortgage Investors - Correspondence, Prospectus, 1965-1972 (Box 392, Folder 5)
  - Continental Mortgage Investors - Second Amendatory Agreement, 1975 March (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Continental Mortgage Investors - Bankruptcy file, 1976 (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - Continental Mortgage Investors - Financing, 1976 (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Continental Mortgage Investors - Waivers 1974/1975 Consents Loan Agreement, 1975 Bank Loan Agreement (Box 393, Folder 3)
  - Continental Mortgage Investors - Original Financing and Purchase Agreement, 1967-1974 (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Vernon Grudge, 1973-1976 (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Cummins Engine Company - Loan Agreement, 1965 (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Cutler Hammer, Inc., 1967 (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Data 100 - Investment Agreements, 1971 (Box 394, Folder 4)
  - Data 100 - Security Transactions - Rule 144, 1975 (Box 394, Folder 5)
  - Data 100 - General, 1976-1978 (Box 394, Folder 6)
  - Data 100 - Investment Agreement, Data 100/Iomec Merger, 1975 (Box 394, Folder 7)
  - Data 100 - Mergers - Compat Corp., 1970-1973 (Box 394, Folder 8)
  - Data 100 - Iomec Agreement - Plan of Reorganization, 1975-1976 (Box 395, Folder 1)
  - Data 100 - Prospectus, 1972-1977 (Box 395, Folder 2)
  - Thomas J. Davis, 1961-1968 (Box 395, Folder 3)
    formerly Davis & Rock.
  - EOCOM Corp. - Investment Agreement, 1974-1977 (Box 395, Folder 4)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Agreement, 1976-1977 (Box 395, Folder 5)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Agreement - Western Litho Plate Co., 1975-1976 (Box 395, Folder 6)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Purchase Agreement, 1973 (Box 396, Folder 1)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Agreement - Voting Trust Newmarket, 1976 (Box 396, Folder 2)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Board of Directors - Agendas, 1973-1976 (Box 396, Folder 3)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 396, Folder 4)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1974 (Box 396, Folder 5-6)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1975 (Box 397, Folder 1-2)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1976 (Box 397, Folder 3-5)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1977 (Box 397, Folder 6, Box 398, Folder 1)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Brentwood Associates, 1972-1974 (Box 398, Folder 2)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 398, Folder 3)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Financial - Audit, 1972-1977 (Box 398, Folder 4)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Financial - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 398, Folder 5)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Financing, 1977 (Box 398, Folder 6)
    1977 Year of Merger
  - EOCOM Corp. - Financing - Promissory Note, 1975 October (Box 398, Folder 7)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Financing, 1973-1976 (Box 399, Folder 1)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Private Placement, 1972-1973 (Box 399, Folder 2-3)
  - EOCOM Corp. - General, 1973-1979 (Box 399, Folder 4)
  - EOCOM Corp. - W. R Grace Agreement Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 400, Folder 1)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Marketing, 1975-1977 (Box 400, Folder 2)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Mergers - General, 1974-1977 (Box 400, Folder 3-4)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Mergers - American Hoechst, 1975-1978 (Box 401, Folder 1-4, Box 402, Folder 1)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Peter O. Crisp Notes and Files, 1975-1977 (Box 402, Folder 2-3)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Mergers - Information International, 1974-1977 (Box 402, Folder 4, Box 403, Folder 1)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Mergers - Muirhead, 1976-1977 (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Patent, 1976-1977 (Box 403, Folder 3)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Stockholders, 1973-1977 (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Stock Option, 1976 (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - EOCOM Corp. - Legal - Brentwood Associates - Preffered Stock Purchase Agreement, 1973 (Box 404, Folder 2-3)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings, 1976 (Box 404, Folder 4-5, Box 405, Folder 1-3, Box 406, Folder 1-4, Box 407, Folder 1-2)
    Audit Committee in addition to Board of Directors meetings.
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings, 1977 (Box 407, Folder 3-4, Box 408, Folder 1-4, Box 409, Box 410)
    Finance/Audit Committee ib addition to Board of Directors meetings.
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors and Finance Committee Meetings, 1978 (Box 411, Folder 1-4, Box 412, Box 413)
    Finance/Audit Committee in addition to Board of Directors Meetings.
  - Eastern Mountain Sports - Financial, 1971-1978 (Box 414, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Mountain Sports - Financing, 1972-1973 (Box 414, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Mountain Sports - General, 1966-1976 (Box 414, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Mountain Sports - Stockholders, 1972-1976 (Box 414, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Mountain Sports - SEC, 1976 (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Eidal International Corp. - General, 1971-1973 (Box 414, Folder 5)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Summary, 1970 (Box 414, Folder 6)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Agreement, 1969-1974 (Box 415, Folder 1)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws, 1971 (Box 415, Folder 2)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Financial, 1970-1975 (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Financing, 1971 (Box 415, Folder 4)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Financing, 1973 (Box 415, Folder 5)
  - Electroprint Inc. - General, 1970-1973 (Box 415, Folder 6)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Investment Memorandum, 1968-1971 (Box 415, Folder 7)
  - Electroprint Inc. - Stockholders, 1971-1976 (Box 415, Folder 8)
  - Fansteel - Financial Audits and Subordinated Debentures, 1967-1977 (Box 415, Folder 9)
  - Fansteel - Shareholders, Stockholders, 1968-1976 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Equity Corporation, 1947-1971 (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Farrington Manufacturing Co., 1971-1973 (Box 416, Folder 3)
  - GAB Services, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 416, Folder 4)
  - GAB Senrices, Inc. - Financial Correspondence and Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 416, Folder 5)
  - GAB Senrices, Inc. - General, 1973 (Box 416, Folder 6)
  - GAB Senrices, Inc. - Merger File, 1975-1977 (Box 417, Folder 1)
  - Glens Falls National Bank and Trust Company, 1971 (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - Bank of Hawaii - Note Purchase Agreement, 1964 (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Hertz Foundation, 1968-1973 (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - Hillman Coal and Coke Company, 1959-1960; 1969-1973 (Box 417, Folder 5-6)
  - Hilo Electric Light Company Ltd., 1941-1973 (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Inner City Merchandisers, 1972-1976 (Box 418, Folder 3)
  - Inner City Merchandisers - Financial, 1973-1978 (Box 418, Folder 4)
  - Intel - Agreements, 1968-1976 (Box 418, Folder 5)
  - Intel - Security Transactions Rule 144, 1973-1975 (Box 419, Folder 1-3)
  - Intel - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 419, Folder 4)
  - Intel - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1968-1973 (Box 419, Folder 5)
  - Intel - Financial - Audits, 1968-1973 (Box 419, Folder 6)
  - Intel - Financing, 1968-1974 (Box 419, Folder 7)
  - Intel - Prospectus, 1971-1976 (Box 420, Folder 1)
  - Intel - Shareholders, 1971-1976 (Box 420, Folder 2)
  - Intel - Stock Option Plan, 1969-1973 (Box 420, Folder 3)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Investment Agreement, 1975-1978 (Box 420, Folder 4)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Agreements, 1976 (Box 420, Folder 5)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 420, Folder 6)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Board of Directors - Meetings, 1976-1978 (Box 420, Folder 7)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Financial - Audits, 1975 (Box 420, Folder 8)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Financial - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 420, Folder 9)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Financing - Investment Memo, 1975 December (Box 420, Folder 10)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Financing - Closing, 1975 December (Box 420, Folder 11)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - General, 1975-1977 (Box 420, Folder 12)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Handwritten notes, 1976-1977 (Box 421, Folder 1)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Marketing Business Plan, 1976-1980 (Box 421, Folder 2)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Mergers - General, 1976-1980 (Box 421, Folder 2A)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Shareholders Meetings, 1977 (Box 421, Folder 3)
  - International Diagnostic Technology - Stockholders Inc., 1977 (Box 421, Folder 4)
  - Iowa Electric Light and Power, 1961 (Box 421, Folder 5)
  - Invest Fund, Inc., 1967-1971 (Box 421, Folder 6)
  - Kaiser Cement and Gypsum Corp. - Audits, 1966-1972 (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Kaiser Cement and Gypsum Corp. - Notes, 1962-1969 (Box 422, Folder 2-3)
  - Kaiser Cement and Gypsum Corp. - Agreements, Bank Credit Agreements, SEC, 1965-1971 (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - Investment Agreement, 1969-1975 (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - Audits, 1969-1975 (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - Financial - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 423, Folder 2)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - Financing, 1969 (Box 423, Folder 3)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - General, 1970-1974 (Box 423, Folder 4)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - Mergers - Cutler Hammer, 1975 (Box 423, Folder 5)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - Stockholders, 1970-1975 (Box 423, Folder 6)
  - Kasper Instruments, Inc. - Closing papers, 1969 (Box 424, Folder 1)
  - Robert Kemp, 1960-1966 (Box 423, Folder 7)
  - Ernest Lagelbauer, 1963-1975 (Box 423, Folder 8)
  - Landtect Corporation - General, 1969-1978 (Box 423, Folder 9)
  - Landtect Corporation - Beckett Associates, 1971-1974 (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - Lykes Youngstown Corporation - 1969 Merger of Lykes Corp. to Youngstown Sheet and Tube (Box 425, Folder 2)
  - Lykes Youngstown Corporation - Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 425, Folder 3)
  - Lykes Youngstown Corporation - SEC, 1968-1970 (Box 424, Folder 2)
  - Magna Corporation - Investment Agreements, 1975-1977 (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Magna Corporation - Summary, 1977 (Box 425, Folder 5)
  - Magna Corporation - Annual Reports, 1968-1975 (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Magna Corporation - Competitors, 1974-1976 (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - Magna Corporation - Notes and Clippings, 1976-1979 (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Magna Corporation - Chronology for Conversations with Pappas, Peter O. Crisp, 1974-1975 (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Magna Corporation - Financial Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 426, Folder 3)
  - Magna Corporation - Financial to Shareholders, 1967-1976 (Box 426, Folder 4)
  - Magna Corporation - Financing, 1975 (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - Magna Corporation - RASI Closing, 1975 (Box 426, Folder 6)
  - Magna Corporation - General, 1968-1975 (Box 426, Folder 7)
  - Magna Corporation - Investment Memo (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Magna Corporation - Marketing, 1974 (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - Magna Corporation - Mergers, 1975-1977 (Box 427, Folder 3)
  - Magna Corporation - Shareholders, 1974 (Box 427, Folder 4)
  - Mathematica, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 427, Folder 5)
  - Francis Mechner, 1968-1969 (Box 427, Folder 6)
  - Mesalina Project, 1972 (Box 427, Folder 7)
  - Mitre Corporation, 1972-1979 (Box 424, Folder 3)
  - Mountain Artisans, 1974-1977 (Box 424, Folder 4)
  - Multrum Project - Offering Circular, 1973-1975 (Box 424, Folder 5)
  - Multrum Project, 1972-1974 (Box 428, Folder 1-2)
  - North American Development Corp. - Annual Reports and Proxies, 1969-1974 (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - North American Development Corp. - Financial, 1972-1976 (Box 428, Folder 4)
  - North American Development Corp. - General, 1970-1976 (Box 428, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1962-1966 (Box 424, Folder 6)
  - Ocean Science Capital Corp., 1965-1976 (Box 424, Folder 7)
  - National Astro Laboratories - Comtel Corp. Exchange of Stock, Reorganization Plan, 1968-1969 (Box 429, Folder 1)
  - National Astro Laboratories - 1961 Material (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - National Astro Laboratories - Metrolonics Assoc. Legal Agreements, 1968 (Box 429, Folder 3)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Financing - Public, 1972 September 21 (Box 429, Folder 4)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Financing - Agreement Drafts, 1968 January 25 (Box 429, Folder 5)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Agreement - U.S. Gypsum Option - Release and Sale of Stock, 1967-1972 (Box 430, Folder 1)
  - Plasmachem, Inc. - Public Offering Documents, 1973 (Box 430, Folder 2-3)
  - Playback Associates - Investment Agreement, 1976 (Box 430, Folder 4)
  - Playback Associates - Agreement, 1972-1976 (Box 431, Folder 1-3)
  - Playback Associates - Board of Directors - Meetings - Minutes, 1972-1978 (Box 431, Folder 4)
  - Playback Associates - Board of Directors - Meetings - Agendas, 1972-1978 (Box 431, Folder 5)
  - Eden Editions - Board of Directors - Agendas, 1971-1972 (Box 432, Folder 1)
  - Playback Associates - Correspondence, Notes, 1976 (Box 432, Folder 2)
  - Playback Associates - Financial - Audits, 1971-1976 (Box 432, Folder 3)
  - Playback Associates - Financial - Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 432, Folder 4)
  - Playback Associates - Financial - Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 432, Folder 5)
  - Playback Associates - Financing, 1976 May (Box 432, Folder 6)
  - Playback Associates - Reorganization, 1972 May 15 (Box 432, Folder 7)
  - Playback Associates - Financing, 1972 June 20 (Box 433, Folder 1)
  - Eden Editions - Financing, 1971 May 18 (Box 433, Folder 2)
  - Playback Associates - General, 1971-1977 (Box 433, Folder 3)
  - Playback Associates - Marketing, 1974-1975 (Box 433, Folder 4)
  - Playback Associates - Mergers, 1972-1977 (Box 433, Folder 5, Box 434, Folder 1-3)
  - Playback Associates - Mergers - Prospectus, 1973 (Box 434, Folder 4, Box 435, Folder 1)
  - Playback Associates - Mergers - Intervision, Inc., 1973 (Box 435, Folder 2)
  - Playback Associates - Mergers - Reeves Teletape, 1976-1979 (Box 435, Folder 3-5, Box 436, Folder 1-2)
  - Playback Associates - Proposals to Customers, 1973 (Box 436, Folder 3)
  - Playback Associates - Stockholders, 1975-1978 (Box 436, Folder 4)
  - Playback Associates - Stock Option Plan, 1969-1978 (Box 436, Folder 5)
  - Playback Associates - Product Literature, 1970s (Box 436, Folder 6, Box 437, Folder 1-2)
  - Real Estate, 1969-1976 (Box 437, Folder 3)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Investment Agreement, 1973-1976 (Box 437, Folder 4)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Investment Agreement (Richcraft), 1974-1975 (Box 437, Folder 5)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Handwritten Notes, 1973-1975 (Box 437, Folder 6)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Board of Directors, 1974-1976 (Box 438, Folder 1)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Financial - Audits, 1975 (Box 438, Folder 2)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Financial - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 438, Folder 3)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Financing - Private, 1975 (Box 438, Folder 4)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Financing - Exercise of Option, 1975 (Box 438, Folder 5)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Financing, 1973 December (Box 438, Folder 6)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Private Placement, 1972-1975 (Box 438, Folder 7)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Financing - Investment Memo, 1973-1975 (Box 439, Folder 1)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - General, 1972-1978 (Box 439, Folder 2)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Marketing, 1975 (Box 439, Folder 3)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Mergers - Agreements, 1975 (Box 439, Folder 4)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Mergers - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 439, Folder 5)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Cummins - Cornelius H. Borman (CHB) File, 1973-1975 (Box 439, Folder 6)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Stockholders, 1973-1975 (Box 440, Folder 1)
  - Rotomaster, Inc. - Stock Options, 1973-1975 (Box 440, Folder 2)
  - Seaboard World Airlines, 1960-1976 (Box 440, Folder 3)
  - Security National Bank of Long Island, 1975 (Box 440, Folder 4)
  - Suemeg Corporation, 1967-1978 (Box 440, Folder 5-6)
  - Taxation of Capital Study - J. R. Dilworth (JRD) File, 1971-1974 (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Tax Reform Information - J. R. Dilworth (JRD) File, 1969 (Box 441, Folder 2-4, Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Thermo Electron - Board of Directors Meetings, 1973-1977 (Box 442, Folder 2-5, Box 443, Folder 1-3)
  - Trans Canada Pipe Line, 1967-1972 (Box 443, Folder 4)
  - UMF Systems, Inc. - Agreements, 1971-1972 (Box 444, Folder 1-2)
  - UMF Systems, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 444, Folder 3)
  - UMF Systems, Inc. - Financial (Box 444, Folder 4)
  - UMF Systems, Inc. - Financing, 1971 June 4 (Box 444, Folder 5)
  - UMF Systems, Inc. - General, 1972-1977 (Box 444, Folder 6)
  - UMF Systems, Inc. - Stockholders, 1970s (Box 444, Folder 7)
  - UMF Systems, Inc. - Sale of Venrock Holdings, 1976 December (Box 444, Folder 8)
  - Vacu-Dry Company, 1965-1972 (Box 445, Folder 1)
  - Ventron Corp. - Agreement - Nippon Soda Japan, 1972-1974 (Box 445, Folder 2)
  - Ventron Corp. - Annual Reports, 1966-1974 (Box 445, Folder 3)
  - Ventron Corp. - Financial, 1968-1976 (Box 445, Folder 4)
  - Ventron Corp. - General, 1967-1977 (Box 445, Folder 5)
  - Ventron Corp. - ABE Hand written notes, 1976-1977 (Box 445, Folder 6)
  - Ventron Corp. - Prospectus, 1968-1973 (Box 445, Folder 7)
  - Ventron Corp. - Stockholders, 1967-1974 (Box 445, Folder 8)
  - Virginia National Building Corp., 1965-1970 (Box 445, Folder 9)
  - Western Maryland Railway Company, 1965-1978 (Box 445, Folder 10)
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 5, 1939-1983; 5; 33.22 Cubic Feet 82 letter document boxes, 4 legal document boxes, and 1 half-letter document box.
  - Opcoa, Inc. - Board of Directors Meetings, 1969-1973 (Box 458, Folder 1)
  - AVX Corporation - Board of Directors, 1976 (Box 458, Folder 2)
  - AVX Corporation - Board of Directors, 1977-1978 (Box 458, Folder 3)
  - AVX Corporation - Mergers - Opcoa, Inc., 1969-1973 (Box 458, Folder 4, Box 459, Folder 1)
  - AVX Corporation - SEC, 1973-1979 (Box 459, Folder 2)
  - Allis Chalmers - Purchase Agreement, 1969 March 3 (Box 459, Folder 3)
  - Allis Chalmers - White Consolidated, 1971 (Box 459, Folder 4)
  - American European Associates - Agreement, 1973 (Box 460, Folder 1)
  - American European Associates - General, 1975-1979 (Box 460, Folder 2)
  - American European Associates - Coke Investors, Inc., 1978 (Box 460, Folder 3)
  - American European Associates - Crutcher Resources, 1976-1979 (Box 460, Folder 4)
  - American Heritage Project, 1979 (Box 461, Folder 1)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Agreement - Oak Hill Sportswear, Inc., 1979 (Box 461, Folder 2)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Agreement - Standby Purchase Agreement, 1977 (Box 461, Folder 3)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Agreement - Credit Agreement, 1977 (Box 461, Folder 4)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Agreement - Exchange Agreement, 1975 (Box 461, Folder 5)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Agreement - Surrender and Exchange Agreement, 1979 (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Agreement - Patents, 1973-1974 (Box 462, Folder 2)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Rights Offering, 1977 (Box 462, Folder 3)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Agreement - Note Agreement, 1972 September 29 (Box 462, Folder 4)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1971-1979 (Box 462, Folder 5)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Bio Kinetics Corp., 1974-1976 (Box 462, Folder 6)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Board of Directors, 1976 (Box 463, Folder 1)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - By-Laws, 1975 (Box 463, Folder 2)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Confidential Memo, 1973-1974 (Box 463, Folder 3)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Financial Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 463, Folder 4)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Financial, 1971-1979 (Box 463, Folder 5)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Financial - SEC, 1979 (Box 463, Folder 6)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Financing, 1977 (Box 463, Folder 7)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Financing - Original Investment Memo, 1972 July 21 (Box 464, Folder 1)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - General Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 464, Folder 2-3)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Product Literature, 1980 (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Marketing, 1974-1976 (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Prospectus, 1972-1977 (Box 465, Folder 2)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Inc. - Stockholders, 1972-1977 (Box 465, Folder 3)
  - Boschert, Inc. - Acquisition by BICC California Acquisition Corp., 1981 March 19 (Box 446, Folder 1)
  - Boschert, Inc. - Board of Directors, 1976-1980 (Box 446, Folder 2-3)